SAI PRAKASH GUPTHA. NEELISETTY

Banglore, Hebbal Ganga nagar +91 8977491569 prakashguptha7@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Having 2+ Years of experience in developing Web Applications. looking for a challenging role in a reputable organization to utilize my technical skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the IT sector.

EXPERIENCE

Nvest Campus

React developer June 2020 - Till Date

Naberly Technologies Pvt Ltd

Software developer June 2018 - May 2020

PROJECTS

Nvest Campus

Instaforms, Maxous

Creating new features, functionality and capabilities on the responsive websites based on forms.

Implementing mobile first approach for existing websites.

Developing mobile application on the crypto currency trading platform using React Native.

Technologies Used: React.js,scss, libraries like ant design, react-bootstrap, React Native.

Professional Links

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/saiprakashguptha/

GitHub:

https://github.com/ prakashguptha7

Naberly Technologies Pvt Ltd

Sai Krupa Traders(Shopping Site)

Sai krupa traders is a cotton bags manufacture company. We made a ecommerce website customers can see all products and added product to cart and wishlist and also developed Admin dashboard to manage customers, products, orders etc.

Technologies Used for website: Angularjs, HeidiSQL, Nodejs, Express. **Technologies Used for dashboard**: Reactis, HeidiSQL, Nodejs, Express.

Tools: Visual studio code, Postman, GitHub.

Role: Worked as a front-end developer and Worked on Add Cart, Remove Cart Apis in Backend.

Developed Three Admin Dashboards for Websites

Admin dashboard is used to manage users. Change the category of user and their catogeries. Display all actions by category and change user status and edit etc.

Technologies used: C#, Android, Document dB, ReactJS.

Tools: Visual studio 17, Microsoft Azure DocumentDB, Postman, GitHub.

Role: Worked as a front end developer for dashboard.

princeNprinces Matrimony

princenprincess Matrimony pioneered in providing Personalized Match Making as well as online match making services. We follow the Indian traditional Match Making System with the help of latest technology to help the individuals to find their soul mates.

Technologies used: C#, AngularJS, CSS, Bootstrap, HTML5, Mongodb. **Tools**: Visual studio 17,Robo 3T, Azure, Visual studio code, Postman,

GitHub.

Role: Worked as a front-end developer.

Nimbole

Nimbole to provide you with cost effective software solutions powered by new age technologies. Our current offerings are hosted on the cloud and delivered on mobile devices. Since the solutions we offer are available on open platforms and the most commonly used ones, our unique features enable integration with your ERP software. **Technologies used**: C#, Angular4, CSS, HTML5, SQL.

Tools: Visual studio 17, Azure, Visual studio code, Postman, GitHub.

Role: Worked as a Jr. Front end developer.

Shiv sena, Nova, Stv9, Zelar Soft

Shiv sena is political party website, Nova is a school website, stv9 is showing list of events in website, Zelar soft is software company website. These projects are the single page applications that I worked On GUI.

Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, bootstrap, javascript and jquery. **Tools**: Visual studio code, GitHub.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web technologies:

Main Skills: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, ES6, Angularjs, Angular2

and Above, Reactis, REST API, NPM.

Intermediate Level: React Native, Node.js, Express, EJS.

DataBase: MySQL, Mongodb.

Hybrid Framework: lonic cordova.

Desktop Framework: electron

Website Tools: Wordpress.

Application Softwares: MS Office, Git desktop.

EDUCATION

QIS College Of Engineering And Technology

Computer Science Engineering 64%

2014 - 2018

Sri prathibha junior college

MPC 74% 2014

Sri Gurudatta high school

SSC 7.8 GPA 2012

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS PERSONAL PROFILE

Received certification on Web application development basics issued by NPTEL[IIT Madras].

Intensive training Certification by tosion on php &,Web designing. Short term course Certification on Oracle database.

MTA: Introduction to Programming Using Python - Certified 2018 by Microsoft .

Attended 'MEAN STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT' Course in ForceEdu.

Date of Birth : 26/08/1997

Marital Status : Single

Nationality : INDIA

Known Languages : English, Telugu, Hindi

Passport : P8042295

DECLARATION

I here by declare that all details furnished above are true to best of my knowledge. if you given opportunity, I would perform up to the best of your expectations.